[Music]
twenty years ago
hampton de ville was formed when my
company merged with another company
owned by a one parker hampton now
he and i could never see our uh hampton
is five two
and blind i'll spay you the details
suffice to say
he and i got into a petty disagreement
over measly one million dollars now
hampton was raised poor so he has always
counted nickels and cents like some of
the keynesian penny pincher
even after he was a billionaire many
times over a miserable little prick has
made it clear
that if i don't pay him that million
dollars
he's going to come after me with all
he's got so
i need you boys to deliver this
briefcase to him at the deville
suites jackson link six hours north
now this is extremely important to me
i care about this more than
family no not family
friends i'm more of a seinfeld guy
oh this is so hard yeah what is
important to the life the uh
the power of seduction no i kind of care
about football because it's the only
thing i can talk about with my father
gourmet dining i'll give her some more
thought the point is
don't this up
okay but what happens if we do
[Music]
jesus
combos really jake don't judge me i'm in
vacation mode
some people cheat in their significant
others while they're out of town i eat
combos
i got a lot of scratcher as well well
there goes two dollars you never get
back
wait what it's never coming back oh no
my two dollars well if you don't start
thinking about these things now you
won't have any money for retirement i
won't be able to retire now i'm so
worried i'll have to work too long after
i'm dead
oh uh no thanks we got it oh
no problem sir have a great stay
you got to stay on your toes if you're
not careful hotels will bleed you dry
i always have to tipper jesus christ man
the whole point of hotels is to make
other people do stuff for you
it's like being a kid before you realize
your parents are human beings and you're
destroying their lives
here are your keys and all i need now is
a credit card
wait i thought the room was paid for yes
the card covers you in case of
incidentals for example you might
incidentally enjoy some of our hotel's
top shelf pornography
or you might incidentally destroy one of
our fine toilets
on vacation maybe we'll do both jay
could you give him your credit card
i drove
you're gonna be okay buddy who's my big
boy
i'm your big boy correct oh and there's
a note here for you from someone named
hampton
i've been delayed i will meet you
tomorrow morning at 9 30 sharpen the
business center
hampton sweet we have the own life to
ourselves
hey where's the luggage where's the
briefcase got him right here sir
you slick elevators this way
gentlemen
i drove so you're tipping her